<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>com.obsproject.Studio.Plugin.BackgroundRemovalLite</id>
  <extends>com.obsproject.Studio</extends>
  <name>Background Removal Lite</name>
  <summary>Background Removal Lite for OBS Studio</summary>
  <description>
    Background Removal Lite is a lightweight and easy-to-use plugin for OBS
    Studio that allows you to remove the background from your webcam feed without
    the need for a green screen. It uses advanced AI technology to accurately
    detect and remove the background, leaving you with a clean and professional
    look.
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/kaito-tokyo/obs-backgroundremoval-lite</url>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.5.1" date="2025-09-27">
      <description>
        <p>This release adds unofficial Flatpak build instructions, improves documentation, and fixes installer links.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Flatpak build instructions added.</li>
          <li>Documentation improvements.</li>
          <li>Installer link corrections.</li>
          <li>Project cleanup.</li>
          <li>Arch Linux PKGBUILD & Flatpak metadata updates.</li>
          <li>Release process & contributor docs enhanced.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.5.0" date="2025-09-27">
      <description>
        <p>This release adds support for Arch Linux packaging, includes a new Flatpak manifest, and brings several documentation and workflow improvements.</p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Arch Linux Packaging Support:</strong> Added a PKGBUILD for easier building and installation on Arch Linux.</li>
          <li><strong>Flatpak Manifest Added:</strong> New experimental Flatpak manifests for easier packaging.</li>
          <li><strong>Documentation & Readme Improvements:</strong> Updated documentation to include Arch Linux instructions.</li>
          <li><strong>Workflow Improvements:</strong> CI workflow now triggers on both branch and tag pushes.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.3" date="2025-09-27">
      <description>
        <p>This update brings several improvements to build and testing workflows, a cleanup of legacy update checker code, and small quality-of-life fixes for both users and contributors. Major changes include renaming the project to "Background Removal Lite", removing the built-in update checker, and cleaning up the CMake and CI build processes. An unsupported PKGBUILD for Arch Linux has also been added.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
